Guide to the Campus Groups Reference Collection, 1892-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Campus Groups Reference collection 1892-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.7 Linear Feet approx. 700 Items
The Campus Groups Reference Collection contains files of printed matter and records that document the activities of formal and informal campus-based associations and groups. This collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Campus Groups Reference Collection was acquired by the University Archives over time.
Collection Overview
The Campus Groups Reference Collection documents activities of formal and informal campus-based associations and groups of people, such as clubs and ethnic groups. The collection includes flyers and newsletters, memoranda, announcements, clippings, membership lists, financial records and other material.
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Administrative Women's Network, 1986-1993 (Box 1)
  - Asians and Asian-Americans, 1920-
  - Association of Clerical and Technical Support Staff (ACTSS), 1980-1981
  - Campus Club, 1971-2001
  - Community Sing, 1936-1937
  - Duke University Federal Credit Union, 1968-
  - Duke Forum, 1964-1966
  - Duke Management Club, 1974-1999
  - Duke University Federal Credit Union, 1968-
  - Duke University Retiree Association, clippings, circa 1984-1987
  - Duke University Retiree Association, flyers, etc., circa 1984-2000
  - Employees, individual
  - International students, general
  - Jews, 1911-
  - Latins and Hispanics, 1929-
  - Native Americans, 1892-
  - Octopus Club
  - The Playreading Group, 1956-1957
  - Phi Beta Kappa [honorary], Duke chapter
  - Samuel Dubois Cook Society, 1998-
  - Saturday Luncheon Club, records, 1948-1974 (2 folders)
  - Saturday Luncheon Club, membership, 1958-1969
  - Sigma Xi [honorary], Duke chapter
  - The Society of Book Collectors and Book Lovers of Duke University, [1964]
  - Town and Campus Club, Constitution and Bylaws, undated
  - University Center for Lesbian, Gay and Biesxual Life, 1995
  - Wednesday Luncheon Club, 1979
  - Women at Trinity and Duke
  - Women's Center, 1993-
  - Workers' Chronicle